Contact

cdenglert@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/chrisenglert-rn-cen-nrp-ccemt-p-fpc-804746114 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Fire fighter
Flight paramedic
Critical Care

Chris Englert RN, CEN, NRP, CCEMT-P, FP-C

Emergency Room Nurse at Memorial Hermann Hospital System Cypress, Texas

Summary

I am a registered nurse and experienced flight paramedic with approximately 12 years of experience in the pre-hospital environment. I am dedicated to the safe and efficient care of my patients while always molding to the cutting edge changes of medicine. The care of my patients is the forefront of what I do and I strive to provide the best care possible.

Experience

Memorial Hermann Health System 2 years 5 months

Registered Nurse Emergency Department July 2019 - Present (11 months)

Views and opinions posted by myself and others are not necessarily those of Memorial Hermann or anything involved in the Memorial Hermann Health System.

Paramedic

January 2018 - July 2019 (1 year 7 months)

Views and opinions posted by myself and others are not necessarily those of Memorial Hermann or anything involved in the Memorial Hermann Health System.

Baylor Scott & White Health Registered Nurse Emergency Department February 2020 - Present (4 months)

REACH Air Medical Services
Crew Chief/Flight Paramedic/Education Coordinator
February 2017 - July 2019 (2 years 6 months)
Houston, Texas

Views and opinions posted by myself and others are not necessarily those of REACH Air Medical Service or anything involved in REACH Air Medical Service.

North Cypress Medical Center Hospital ER Tech/Paramedic February 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 8 months)

AirMed Regional Houston Flight Paramedic/Base Educator August 2015 - August 2016 (1 year 1 month) Houston, Texas

Montgomery County Hospital District Paramedic/Adjunct Instructor January 2009 - July 2016 (7 years 7 months) Conroe, Texas

Lone Star College Clinical Preceptor October 2010 - March 2016 (5 years 6 months) Conroe, Texas

EagleMed LLC
Flight Paramedic/Base Educator
February 2014 - October 2014 (9 months)
Houston, Texas

Cypress Creek Volunteer Fire Department Fire Fighter June 2005 - April 2012 (6 years 11 months) Cypress, Texas

Fire and Rescue

Cypress Creek EMS
Paramedic
April 2007 - August 2009 (2 years 5 months)
Houston, Texas

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington Master of Science in Nursing Education · (2019 - 2020)

Lone Star College
Associate of Science (A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2018 - 2019)

Cypress Creek EMS
Paramedic Certificate, Paramedicine